trustdirectory.org 2008-05-24

# www.trustdirectory.org - Privacy Policy

## Updated August 2006

 _Generally www.trustdirectory.org does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information except in very specific instances, such as, for example, when you provide your email address to receive specialized services). Whenever we collect such information, you will have a choice regarding whether to provide it, how it will be used, and to whom it will be disclosed. The instances in which www.trustdirectory.org does collect and use information are specifically described below in this Privacy Policy._

www.trustdirectory.org provides a comparison shopping service that enables consumers to compare prices, products and stores when they shop online. These services are provided by www.trustdirectory.org which is a wholly owned subsidiary of 2007-2008 all rights reserved., Inc (" 2007-2008 all rights reserved."). 2007-2008 all rights reserved. values its users and their concerns about privacy. To this end, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. engages in consistent information practices and uses its best efforts to make clear disclosures regarding those practices. This Privacy Policy is a part of that effort.

What does this Privacy Policy cover?  
This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by 2007-2008 all rights reserved.. If there are any exceptions, we will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information.

Please be aware that, as part of the Services, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. may provide links to Web sites operated by third parties. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications.

What information does 2007-2008 all rights reserved. collect and how is it used? Does 2007-2008 all rights reserved. disclose information to third parties?   
2007-2008 all rights reserved. may collect any or all of the following three types of information: (a) traffic or clickstream data, (b) cookies, or (c) contact information and other personally identifying information. 2007-2008 all rights reserved.'s collection and use of each type of data is described below, as well as the ways (if any) in which the data may be shared with third parties.

 _(a) Traffic or Clickstream Data._ Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our Web site, or searched our site for a specific product. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) users access. For example, 2007-2008 all rights reserved.'s servers collect information about the site to which you may depart to enable 2007-2008 all rights reserved. to calculate and receive payments from its partners. In addition, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. uses the information (in aggregate form) to better design the Services.

 _(b) Cookies._ Like many sites, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. collects information about online behavior using cookies. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning, as well as to streamline their experiences using the Services. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies lets us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our business partners. To 2007-2008 all rights reserved., using information within cookies is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. 

_(c) Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information._ 2007-2008 all rights reserved. can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become a Newsletter subscriber, advertiser/merchant with 2007-2008 all rights reserved., provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from 2007-2008 all rights reserved. and provide your name or return contact information, (2) when you register for the advanced features, or (3) in connection with special offers or contests.

Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or clickstream data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request.

Finally, you may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. 2007-2008 all rights reserved. uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. Finally, from time to time, but only with your permission, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. may provide certain of its users' registration information to selected third parties who wish to participate in special promotions offered in conjunction with 2007-2008 all rights reserved.. Users may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by contacting 2007-2008 all rights reserved..

Is data stored by 2007-2008 all rights reserved. secure?   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, 2007-2008 all rights reserved. has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to 2007-2008 all rights reserved. (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that 2007-2008 all rights reserved. will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

Does 2007-2008 all rights reserved. collect personally identifying information from or about children?   
2007-2008 all rights reserved. uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any portions of the Services that require registration.

Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

How can I access or correct any personally identifying information about me?  
To request a copy of the personally identifiable information you have sent to 2007-2008 all rights reserved., please send an email containing your request to [help@www.trustdirectory.org](mailto:help@www.trustdirectory.org). You must provide your full name and the e-mail from which the request is received (and to which the response will be sent) must match the e-mail on file with 2007-2008 all rights reserved.. You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the e-mail.

How do I find out more about 2007-2008 all rights reserved.'s information practices?   
If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact 2007-2008 all rights reserved. as follows: 

E-Mail: [help@www.trustdirectory.org](mailto:help@www.trustdirectory.org)
